<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Luxe Law Group, APC</title>
    <description>You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document  head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site  description.
</description>
    <link>http://luxelawgroup.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://luxelawgroup.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 14:01:39 +0900</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 14:01:39 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Contact</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’d love to hear from you!  Contact us via email at &lt;strong&gt;info@luxelawgroup.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(415) 488-6748&lt;/strong&gt; for Northern California&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(619) 324-3396&lt;/strong&gt; for Southern California&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mailing address is: &lt;strong&gt;104 Washington Avenue, #70601, Point Richmond, CA 94807&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow us on Twitter at &lt;strong&gt;@luxelawgroup&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTICE AND DISCLAIMER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any communication from you does not establish an attorney-client relationship.  An attorney-client relationship can only be established by signing a fee agreement.  Luxe Law Group, APC makes no legal representations. The passing of time may compromise your rights; if you do not retain Luxe Law Group, APC you must immediately seek services from another attorney to protect any rights.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://luxelawgroup.com/contact/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://luxelawgroup.com/contact/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>News</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;January 21, 2017 10:30 am - 12:00 pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Top 5 Estate Essentials&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Atria Tamalpais Creek&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;853 Tamalpais Ave, Novato, CA  94947, United States&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;November 25th, 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen to us on KGO 810 at 4:00 p.m. PSTon Hangin with Langan as we discuss the importance of estate planning. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;KGO 810 – &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kgoradio.com&quot;&gt;http://www.kgoradio.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hanging with Langan - &lt;a href=&quot;http://maureenlangan.com/&quot;&gt;http://maureenlangan.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://luxelawgroup.com/news/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://luxelawgroup.com/news/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Probate / Conservatorships</title>
        <description>&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Successfully represent clients in probates and conservatorships&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Review and draft probate and conservatorship court pleadings&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Draft Inventories &amp;amp; Appraisals for multi-million dollar estates&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Make court appearances&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Prepare Summary Administrations&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Manage accounting experts in court reportings&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Represent professional fiduciaries &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Work directly with bonding services for Conservators and Administrators&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Communicate with medical professionals in order to prepare and defend Capacity Declarations&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Review depositions and prepare comprehensive summaries&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Successfully negotiate dispute settlements&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Render opinions on Estate, Conservator and Trust Administration litigation&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Prepare Small Estate Affidavits&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Communicate with Decedent creditors&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Prepare General Plans of Care for Conservatees&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Represent Decedent estates in corollary litigation matters&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://luxelawgroup.com/probate_conservatorships/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://luxelawgroup.com/probate_conservatorships/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate</title>
        <description>&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Prepare trust transfer deeds&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Conduct chain of title research for real property&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Negotiate, prepare and manage real estate deals &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Oversee real estate transactions within property tax reassessment exclusions&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Provide opinions on best-practice for real estate dealings&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Calculate allocation of property tax exclusions for real properties during trust administrations&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Draft lease agreements&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Prepare escrow instructions&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Negotiate commercial lease agreements&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Review and defend against 3-day notices to quit&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Render opinions concerning &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Real property ownership structures&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Section 1031 exchanges&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Reverse Section 1031 exchanges&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Real estate tax &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://luxelawgroup.com/real_estate/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://luxelawgroup.com/real_estate/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business Transactions</title>
        <description>&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Create and maintain corporations, LLCs, LPs and professional corporations&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Negotiate and draft contracts&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Advise clients regarding start-ups, reorganizations and M&amp;amp;As&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Draft confidentiality agreements&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Counsel concerning licensing and intellectual property  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Confidentially advise on multi-state business matters&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Create multifaceted business entity structures &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Review and counsel concerning governance documents and officer actions in board meetings&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Prepare corporate conversions&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Advise clients concerning multi-million dollar transactions &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Negotiate business acquisitions&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Structure settlements&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Prepare business structure opinions in class-action lawsuits &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Act as general counsel for business associations &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://luxelawgroup.com/business_transactions/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://luxelawgroup.com/business_transactions/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Estate Planning</title>
        <description>&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Counsel clients on complex estate planning matters&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Review and draft succession plans, including but not limited to: &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Revocable trusts &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Life insurance trusts &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Irrevocable trusts &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Charitable trusts &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Special Needs trusts&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Community Property agreements&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Lifetime gifts&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Charitable gift planning&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Prenuptial/postnuptial agreements&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Wills  &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Powers of Attorney&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Advance Health Care Directives&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Direct trust administrations&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Draft opinion letters and memorandums concerning various probate, trust and will matters&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Manage institutional charitable gifting &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Compassionate work with hospice clients&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://luxelawgroup.com/estate_planning/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://luxelawgroup.com/estate_planning/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Legal Team</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;rachel-fetter&quot;&gt;Rachel Fetter&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rachel Fetter has been a certified paralegal for three years, and is a California Notary Public. She received her A.A. in Language Arts and Humanities at College of Marin, Kentfield.  She then attended the American Bar Association approved program at California State East Bay in Hayward, California where she received her Certificate in Paralegal Studies.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prior to graduation, Rachel served as an intern for the California Attorney General’s Office in Oakland, California. There she reported to Senior Legal Specialists and reviewed documents for an Investigative Subpoena regarding a significant state-wide environmental case. She also developed a spreadsheet management system to organize physical document repositories. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After graduation, Rachel worked as an administrative assistant for the real estate firm Scheer Law Group, LLP. There she was responsible for case management research and client communications. She catalogued, indexed and archived recently closed case files. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thereafter Rachel moved to Delfino Green &amp;amp; Green, a personal injury and workers’ compensation firm. She managed the entire operational client process for the attorneys. This included intake interviews, invoicing and collections, as well as hearings and case closing procedures. Rachel regularly engaged with key clients and opposing party counsel. She also reviewed and revised settlement offers for attorney approval. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to pursue an interest in estate planning and broaden her legal expertise, Rachel accepted an opportunity with the Law Offices of Julia P. Wald, a firm specializing in estate planning, trust administration, probate and conservatorships. In that role she interacted with clients, attorneys, outside counsel and courts. 
Rachel reviews and drafts estate planning documents and grant deeds. She also leads online research efforts around real property ownership, calendaring court deadlines and managing filing processes. She is entrusted with firm operations, interviewing potential hires, training new employees, day-to-day banking and financial transactions, and notarizing firm documents. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When away from the office, Rachel volunteers. Her strong sense of empathy and dedication to her community is the driving force behind her volunteer activities and outreach. Rachel’s proven commitment to her firm and her strong relationships within the legal ecosystem have led to her hard-earned reputation as a determined advocate and champion for her clients.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://luxelawgroup.com/legal_team/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://luxelawgroup.com/legal_team/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Legal Team</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;april-c-ball-esq&quot;&gt;April C. Ball, Esq.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;April C. Ball, Esq. has been an attorney for 18 years, and is licensed to practice law in California and New York. She received her B.S. in Accounting at California State University, Northridge.  She attended law school at California Western School of Law and then received her Master of Laws in Taxation from the University of San Diego School of Law.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After graduation, April worked for the accounting firm of KPMG LLP as a tax specialist and then two law firms where she sharpened her transactional law skills, which include: estate planning, probate, conservatorship, tax, corporate, LLC, partnership, ERISA, pension, commercial, , finance, real estate, contract and intellectual property law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She then moved to Grace Hollis Lowe Hanson &amp;amp; Schaeffer LLP in order to create and run the firm’s transactional department.  There, she used her vast knowledge to assist both individual, litigation and business clients in various areas of transactional law.  April also worked as Senior Attorney Editor for Thomson Reuters Westlaw – the premiere legal research and legal know-how company for lawyers throughout the world.  There she drafted complex transactional documents and practice guides concerning multiple areas of California and New York law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;April has operated in her own private practice to serve in Los Angeles, San Diego and the Bay Area since 2008, where she assists law firms, businesses, individuals and families in comprehensive legal planning. Because of her specialized experience, April’s law practice considers the tax implication of each legal transaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of her community outreach, April delivers speeches for community, legal and professional events, as well as seminars and writing engagements.  She has presented on California registered domestic partner law, estate planning, business planning and asset protection for business owners and professionals at various organizations, women’s groups, large national corporations, medical associations, and attorney and judicial groups.  Pro bono legal counseling services are also important to her practice.
April’s service-oriented approach to client matters has earned her recognition from firms, community organizations and clients alike.  She continues to work with individuals, families, athletes, actors, small-business owners and prominent banking establishments in her practice.  Away from the office, April is an elementary school volunteer and assists in leading her local chapter of the Read to Succeed program.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://luxelawgroup.com/legal_team/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://luxelawgroup.com/legal_team/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re different</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We do things differently: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We treat clients the way we want to be treated – like trusted family  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We remove the surprises in billing by using flat-rate fees &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We love to talk to you, so we don’t charge for phone calls  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We come to you – your home, your business or your favorite coffee shop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We represent: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Families&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Small estates&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Business owners&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;High net-worth individuals&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Athletes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Entertainers &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Military&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://luxelawgroup.com/about/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://luxelawgroup.com/about/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
